and who tell you other things.
You can't let them divert you!
If you're going to do it,
then become the best idol
in Japan ever!
Do you always have
to know your future?
Can you not do anything unless
your future is guaranteed?
What's the fun in that?
Didn't you say so yourself?
You didn't want Tomoko
to live her life like that?
That the most important
thing for a woman
is to have more confidence
in herself?
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Thank you.
Takeshi!
We've found a way
to get rid of Onizuka!
What is it?
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Excuse me?
What did you just say?
You see, in one week,
there will be placement exams.
We'd like you to take it
with the students.
Hold on a sec!
I'm a teacher, why do I have
to take the test?
Some of the parents
sent a request.
We know you've been working
well with your class lately.
But they were worried about your
intelligence and education.
Um, of course we told them that
there was nothing to worry about.
But they just wouldn't accept that.
- Right, everyone?
- That's right.
So we made an agreement.
It was decided that the best
solution would be for you
to prove yourself.
Right, everyone?
That's right.
And so, last years average score,
was a total 350 points.
They agreed you should
be able to get 400 points.
Otherwise, they questioned
how this school
would take responsibility.
We found that insulting,
so we told them,
of course, Onizuka-sensei was
willing to stake his job on it.
Are you kidding?
400 points is an average
of 80 per, there's no way!
Well sure, don't you have
confidence in yourself?
Give me a break!
I'll do anything else,
like work the cafeteria or clean.
You'll be fine, Onizuka-sensei.
I'm certain you can do it!
Of course! There's no way
the person teaching would
be stupider than
the students, right?
By the way, I got 490 last year -
an average of 98.
Really?
Um, isn't there some other way?
What!?
Aren't you a man of action?
Of course!
Do your best Onizuka-sensei,
we're behind you all the way!
These are the questions
from last year.
- Take a look.
- Excuse me...
We expect great things,
Onizuka-sensei!
You can count on me!
As a man, I, Onizuka Eikichi
will be number one!
Why is Onizuka going to take
the test with us?
Something about if he doesn't
get over 400 points, he'll be fired.
- Oh no!
- It's okay!
Onizuka graduated from college
and took the teacher's exam.
That's right. He just looks stupid.
Yeah, you're right.
But you know, I heard Onizuka-
sensei the other day.
What?
The 8th Tokugawa shogun
was Matsudiara Ken,
and there isn't a 15th.
And he sounded totally serious.
Hey, this is easier than I thought!
400 points will be a snap!
Especially for someone
who likes studying.
Hey, yeah...
How about going out for a bit?
No need to be so shocked
because of my great scores!
- Oh! Did you think I was stupid!
- It's 100 points.
See! When I want to, I can do it.
That's your total for all five!
Huh? No way!
You must have made
a mistake scoring. See, here.
Here, here, this!
It's not "to cultivate eternity",
it's "to cultivate talent".
Uh, then, here, this English...
Number 3,
it's not "sauzage"?
Sausage!
Did you really graduate
from college?
Well, yes...
What about the teaching exam?
Uh well, I found someone
who looked just like me
who was smart...
Aren't you embarrassed about
doing something like that?!
I had no choice, I wanted
to become a teacher!
- That's not the issue!
- It is!
What do you mean?!
That test is important...
He's stupider then me!
At this rate, he's sure to be fired!
- Here...
- Thank you.
Are you okay?
Takeshi!
Wait, Takeshi!
Excuse me.
I saw Takeshi.
He's alive, Takeshi is alive.
What are you talking about?
He's no ghost!
That's okay if you
don't believe me.
Hold on!
- Get a grip!
- Let me go!
This is great!
This is great Teshigawara-sensei!
What a good idea!
Wish we'd thought of this earlier!
Using his stupidity.
But you know,
is this okay? None of the parents
actually complained.
It'll be okay, once we fax his
results to all of their homes.
There's no question they'll
raise a ruckus!
I see! You've got it all
planned already!
But, what if...
Onizuka gets 400 points?
There's no way.
Not for someone who took
seven years to get out
- of such a third rate college.
- Of course not!
Get serious, Head Teacher!
Or should I say "principal"?
Yes, well...
There's no way he could.
This time,
Onizuka's face will disappear
from this academy.
Well, with Onizuka's intelligence,
he'll get 200 points.
So that's what they're up to!
- Oh! Welcome home!
- What?!
You two still here?
Tonight's your favorite
yakiniku!
- What have you done?!
- Mom and I did this!
Isn't it nice?
It's feels like the real home
of newlyweds.
Where's the videos
that were here?
- Oh, I threw them away.
- Threw them away!?
You don't need them anymore.
- You have me now.
- Oh my!
How could you!
I can't live without those!
Where are you going,
dinners almost ready!
- I'll be right back.
- Really?
You better not be skipping out!
- Are they still there?
- Yeah.
I've told them to go home,
but those two are stubborn.
Let's go.
- Never mind, just come.
- What?
Where we going?
We meet again!
Is something wrong?
Please.
- You're sure?
- Yes, please!
This...
This is the first time I've entered
a woman's place.
That Fuyutsuki-sensei would
suddenly invite me in...
Stop muttering, let's get started.
Oh, but...
even I have to get into the mood.
Sorry, you aren't going to get
any sleep tonight.
I see.
This is my first time, be gentle.
You know you...
Aren't you misunderstanding
something?
Am I?
For this next week, you will be
staying at my place and studying.
How can I let them fire you!
Watch the willpower of a woman!
Yes...
All right, then.
How are you doing?
This is unbelievable, that you
would be cooking for me!
- Dinner's almost ready.
- Okay.
The scent of a woman.
Oh, I shouldn't...
- What are you doing!
- Um, nothing...
- Dinner's ready.
- Huh? What's this?
It's maguro no kabutoyaki.
The eyeballs are rich in DHA
which is good for your brain.
Eat it all now!
- Please clear the table.
- Um...
What's this music that's been
putting me to sleep?
It's alpha music.
It has the power to awaken
hidden abilities in humans.
Um, about this schedule you
gave me earlier.
Even my sleep time is scheduled.
Yes, that's your studying sleep.
I'm going to study even
when I'm sleeping?
Of course! Hey!
It's nonsmoking here.
And besides, until the test,
please stop smoking.
It impedes circulation.
Didn't you know that?
I did not. There's no need
to go that far...
How can you say that!
You've only got one week
until the test!
Yeah, but... how about time
for recreation?
Stop wasting time and eat.
Oh! You're ten minutes behind
schedule already!
Wow, it's beautiful!
That's a cute necklace.
Did someone give it to you?
Oh!
Could it be someone who looks
exactly like me, your boyfriend?
He... liked motorcycles too.
Oh...
Oh, but he wasn't smart
like you, Tôdô-kun.
He was always playing baseball.
Why are you talking about this?
There's a lot of students
who didn't make it
into your high school, Tôdô-kun.
- They're at our school.
- I was just lucky.
And I'm regretting it right now.
- I wish I'd gone to Seirin.
- Why?
Because, then I would have
met you sooner, Miyabi-chan.
Hello? Yeah.
Let everyone know.
The game's started.
What's this disgusting
looking bread?
It's Fuyutsuki-sensei. She's even
got my menu planned out.
There's supposed to be DDT
or something in it.
- That's DHA.
- Shaddap, you.
You're looking kinda pale.
Are you okay, Onitchi?
- I've only slept an hour.
- An hour?
When she catches me slacking,
I lose more and more sleep.
And she doesn't let me eat
when I want!
On top of that, it's no smoking!
I thought it was going
to be heaven, but it's hell.
Onizuka-sensei.
- What are you doing?
- Uh, well, nothing...
Please go home ahead of me.
I'm going to stop by
the pharmacy and buy some
stamina drinks first. Tonight's
another all-nighter.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Cut it out, you make it out
like I'm half dead!
I'm even being given
stamina drinks!
I think I'm gonna explode.
When it comes down to this,
I'm gonna do it!
What are you thinking?
Yeah! Why don't you try
studying for a change?
Shaddap, I don't wanna
hear it from you.
Fuyutsuki, prepare yourself!
- He's gonna be fired for sure!
- What should we do, Nanako?
Oh man, what can I say.
No way can I tell them
I came to get condoms.
Lucky!
Eikichi!
You've finally decided.
- It's always okay with me.
- No, this is for someone else.
What do you mean?
Who's this someone else?
Who is it? Eikichi!
- You mustn't, Eikichi-san...
- What are you doing, Mama!
- Give it to me!
- Give it back!
Quit it!
Oh, you really mustn't,
Eikichi-san!
What are you...
Wh-Why?
Condom?!
You...
With my daughter...
- You've got it all wrong, Papa.
- Papa?!
How did you know we
were here, dear?
- Dear?!
- Why you...
- She's my wife!
- Dear, calm down!
Eikichi...!
- I've got a schedule, gotta go!
- Eikichi!
- I drifted off!
- Please.
Don't worry about me,
go ahead and go to sleep.
Okay then, just for a bit.
- No slacking!
- I know.
The sides abc of a triangle,
ab, ac over respective points,
de, ad, ae 2 point 3...
The time's come.
What?
Stop looking!
It's no good!
I can't concentrate at all like this!
Gotta look at a guy...
Tôdô-kun!
- Sorry, wait long?
- No, I just got here.
Really? That's good.
Yo, Miyabi.
- Someone you know?
- Let's go...
- Hey, thanks!
- For what?
You know, about Tomoko
going to Okinawa.
You talked to her parents, right?
What are you talking about?
But you know, this is great!
- What?
- He's your new boyfriend, right?
That means you're over
Takeshi-kun now.
What does it matter to you?
What's your concern
with Miyabi-chan?
I'm Miyabi's homeroom teacher,
Onizuka Eikichi.
And you?
I'm Tôdô. Tôdô Shin'ichi.
Nice to meet you.
Please.
I've heard about you
from Miyabi-chan.
Sounds like you're quite
a unique teacher.
You've tried to drop
a student from a roof.
You've tried to go on
a compensated
date with a student.
You've forced a student
to drop out of school.
We don't have any teacher's
like that at my school,
- so I couldn't believe it.
- Yeah, well...
So what school you from?
He's in the top ranked
school of this area.
He's the top of his class.
On top of that, his dad's high
in the Ministry of Education.
No way!
Then, maybe you could take
the test for me...
If you can't, then maybe you
could talk to your dad.
My brain's just not
cut out for this.
You know of some way
to get sick quick?
Something that looks real,
but is easy to cure, you know.
He's just as unique
as you said, isn't he?
Ignore him, let's go.
Don't be so cold, Miyabi.
Your teacher's in a bind here!
You...
I've never once considered you
my homeroom teacher.
Excuse us.
- Over here.
- You sure this is okay?
What're we going to do if Onitchi
get's kicked out of school?
But are you sure the questions
are in this safe?
I'm sure they are.
I saw Uchiyamada put it
in here before.
Okay.
You know, I feel like I've really
become a burglar.
Dumb ass! We really are now.
If we can get in,
then Onitchi'll have no problems
memorizing the questions.
On top of that, we can improve
our scores too!
- Alright!
- Who's there?
I figured something like this
would happen,
so I've been waiting.
Must be one of the idiots
from 2-4, right?
- What'll we do?
- Come out!
What's this?
Hey you! You can't get away!
Idiots! If we hadn't
done something,
you guys would have been toast!
- Sorry, Kikuchi-san!
- Hurry!
I've finally gotten the password
to access the main computer.
Wow! I'm not sure what you're
talking about, but it's great!
This way doesn't have any risk.
- There!
- You did it!
Wow, Kikuchi-kun!
All we have to do is get
a printout.
Alright!
Hey, what's going on, Kikuchi?
- Hey, it's gone!
- It can't be!
ACCESS DENIED
Someone's blocking us.
REFUSE THE USER'S ACCESS?
"Principal: kôchô."
"Poison: doku."
Heard that one
somewhere before...
There's no way in hell
I'll get 400 points!
There's no way.
It's no use! I'm not cut out
for studying!
I know my way around
the convenience stores,
or how to connect up a bike,
that's no problem.
Okay then, better look
for a job now.
Yeah?
Sensei, you're in there,
aren't you?
Hurry and come out!
Whaddya want? This is the guys
toilet, you know?
Never mind that! Kikuchi guys
are in trouble!
What?
We know it was you.
Tell us the truth.
Do you have any proof?
- What's with that attitude!
- Hakamada-sensei, it's okay.
- But...
- We'll be generous this time.
Because of it, we we're able
to prevent anything
from happening.
They should realize now.
There's nothing they
can do now.
Right, Kikuchi?
Listen, if we catch you again,
you'll be expelled! Expelled!
'Nuff with the "expelled" already.
- Will you be quiet already.
- What's that attitude?
Sensei.
It was you!
Listen you guys,
never do anything stupid
like this again!
But Onitchi, at this rate...
- Yeah!
- Idiots!
As your teacher,
I can't let the ones in my
charge be in danger.
Besides,
I'll never stop to needing
your sympathy.
Okay then,
who was the 15th Tokugawa
shogun?
Tokugawa?
Yoshinobu.
Alright!
I'll make this a great test!
I'll show 'em my teacherly side!
What happened?
Why're you so into it now?
- Here.
- Thanks.
Those guys got me thinking.
To get 400 points and show
that Uchiyamada.
This reference book is yours.
You mentioned you wanted
to be something
besides being a teacher.
So it was a stewardess?
Seems that there's going to be
an entrance exam soon?
Please don't go snooping
through others' desks!
I did not! Your friend told me
about it on the phone.
Please don't answer my phone!
Well, you were taking a bath...
Anyway, while you're here,
please concentrate only
on your studying!
Yes, ma'am.
Is it wrong?
What is?
You know, to take the exam.
Not really.
If you want me to quit,
you can say so.
Why should I?
Because if I pass,
I'll be quitting school.
Oh, I see.
You don't want to be
separated from me.
Don't be silly!
- I just...
- Just?
No matter how much
of a dream it was to me,
is it okay for me
to do that now?
To do things without worrying
about the consequences,
isn't that what you told Tomoko?
Yes, but...
Unlike Nomura-san,
I'm older now.
Then don't take it.
Don't be so simple minded!
- Then take it.
- Which is it?
Are you going to do
what I tell you?
Are you going to do what
I decide for you?
Hello, this is the Fuyutsuki
residence.
- Hey, don't!
- Oh! Sensei!
- It's me!
- Tomoko!
- Are you doing well?
- Yes!
Between work and lessons,
I'm pooped.
- But I'm hanging in there!
- Alright! Hang in there!
Oh...
But why are you there, Sensei?
Well, you see...
it's Fuyutsuki-sensei.
She begged me to come over.
Don't you dare!
She'll misunderstand!
Hello, Nomura-san?
How are you?
Um, has Miyabi-chan
gone to school?
Aizawa-san?
Not yet.
Don't worry, I think she's going
to return to school soon.
How's everything there?
Are you doing well?
- Have a seat.
- What is it?
You sure it's okay for someone
from another school to be here?
It's okay! Our school doesn't
worry about that at all.
But this really is a great school.
It's nothing like ours.
I don't ever want to go back
to that school.
If I could,
I'd like to stay with you
like this, Tôdô-kun.
But you've got interesting
teachers at Seirin too,
- like that Onizuka-sensei.
- Stop it! Not him!
- Yo, Tôdô!
- I'll introduce you!
Is she your new girlfriend
we heard about?
- Yeah.
- She's quite nice!
Um, my name is Aizawa Miyabi.
Nice to meet you,
I'm Nabeshima.
I've known him since we
were small kids.
I'm Tamaki.
- She's cute, isn't she?
- Yeah.
- Maybe I should try too.
- Hey, butt out!
- Let's go.
- Nice meeting you.
So she's the object of this time's
Cinderella game?
Yeah, seems like Tôdô looks
exactly like someone
- she used to like.
- That's perfect.
This should be good.
Takeshi!
What?
- You should stop seeing him.
- What?
They're up to something.
What do you mean they're
up to something?
I dunno, but it's definitely
not good!
Will you cut it out!
Do you think I'd just believe you
out of the blue like that?
Didn't you say you didn't know
me anymore?
If that's the case, then stop
bugging me.
He looks exactly like Takeshi.
It looks Miyabi's been totally
taken by him.
But what are you going to do?
Those guys from Jinnan Academy
look like trouble.
Should we ask Onizuka?
Right now isn't the time
to bother him.
Ouch!
You too, Noboru?
Sorry.
Where are we going?
I've got a present for you today.
- Really? What is it?
- It's a surprise.
Let's go.
- Alright! Done!
- Okay! Just safe!
Okay, this one next!
History, huh?
Hello, this is Fuyutsuki.
- It's Murai.
- What's wrong?
- C'mon, tell me!
- Just wait!
Is Onizuka there?
He's kind of busy right now.
Tomorrow's the real exam,
so he's practicing right now.
I'm sorry, but could this
wait till later?
I understand, I'll call back later.
Aren't they closed?
What are you doing?
I asked my dad and he
reserved the place.
Really?!
Okay.
Let's go.
- Time's up!
- Okay, done!
All answered, no blanks!
- Take a look!
- Let's see.
For one person to solve this
many problems
is quite an achievement.
I've worked so hard...
How about taking
a bath together?
- I will grade these.
- Oh, no good?
- Can I smoke one?
- Go ahead.
By the way, who was that
call from?
It was Murain-kun.
He said he'd call back later.
Oh, I see.
- Miyabi-chan?
- Yes?
What's going on?
What's wrong, Tôdô-kun?
Sorry, everyone, I win!
The Cinderella game is a bet
I made with these guys.
There's no other reason why
I'd go out with a girl like you.
After midnight,
the magic disappears.
Your kidding, right?
You can do what you
like with her.
- Please, wait!
- Where're you going?
Let me go!
Stop it!
Miyabi, run!
This is great!
You got 83 in math!
- See!
- Here too!
And this, and this!
This is great, Onizuka-sensei!
Isn't it?
Now then...
Time for the hunt.
It's gone!
This is incredible!
Altogether you've scored
over 400 points!
When did this happen,
Onizuka-sensei?
Stop it!
Murai!
- Murai, are you okay?
- Sorry 'bout that.
You see, they're
in the karate club.
Hurry up and get
the video, Nabeshima.
- How cute!
- Hey, this is great!
- Why are you doing this?
- To pass time.
Pass time?
You know, lately, it felt like
we'd die of boredom.
But thanks to you guys,
it's been pretty fun.
- You're terrible!
- You should talk.
You totally fell for it.
Hey, Miyabi!
Where are you?
Princess, have you been injured?
So, Tôdô-kun...
"Not appropriate",
um, what does that mean?
Speak up and tell me.
- It means inappropriate, right?
- Oh yeah, that's right.
That's like what you guys
are doing, isn't it?
Sorry, but...
I've got all this pent-up stress
from all this studying.
Killing time, hmm, you good
for nothing punks.
Just like a yakuza, huh?
Interesting.
If you're going to hit us,
go ahead.
But I'm warning you,
my father is high in the Ministry
of Education.
Oh really? And so?
Anyone who hurt my students -
no matter who - I won't forgive!
Where'd he run off to?
Oh, that's gotta hurt.
- Miyabi, let's go.
- It's gone.
My necklace is gone.
The necklace that Takeshi
gave me is gone!
Let's look for it.
It's not here.
Miyabi, you sure you
came through here?
Think carefully...
Man! It's not here!
Hey!
Are you really sure you
dropped it here?
It's okay already.
Isn't today the test?
You'll be fired because of me.
You know, this is more important
than some test.
Because I'm your homeroom
teacher.
Thank you...
Huh? You say something?
Thank you, Sensei!
Miyabi,
you are the real prince.
Think about it.
Go on!
So, it looks like Onizuka-sensei
ran away after all.
Rather than be embarrassed,
I guess he figured it was
better not to take it.
He would not!
He scored over 400 points on
the practice exam last night.
Then why isn't he here?
Well, I don't know.
In any case, let's report this
to the head teacher.
- Um, please wait a minute!
- What is it?
Um...
You see, I got a phone call
from Onizuka-sensei.
Because he's a teacher,
he said to take the test
without a handicap would
hurt his pride.
- Pride?
- Yes.
He doesn't need five hours,
one hour would be
sufficient time.
Oh, I'm looking forward to that!
Yes, we're looking forward to it!
Did he really call?
- No, I lied.
- What?!
Now then, we will begin soon.
So it looks like Onizuka-sensei
has abandoned the test.
Now you know the truth
about Onizuka-sensei.
He's a coward who runs for it
at the crucial moment.
From now on, you know a man
like him cannot be a teacher.
Forget about him, understand?
Excuse me, Head Teacher,
we'll talk later.
I can finish all five sections
in an hour.
Onizuka-sensei...
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
please, the exam.
Yes!
Oh man, he made a mess!
Don't look at me!
Okay, time's up!
Please pass it forward
from the back.
You haven't written
a single thing!
What are you doing?
Come on, Onizuka-sensei.
Onizuka-sensei?
- Sensei!
- Onizuka-sensei!
No!
2016-08